The very cool thing about the app is
we have like a one -click install with
MCP, you know, Figma is there out of
the box. So it just takes you into
Figma, you just log in and then you go
back and you can use this Figma skill
that we're releasing alongside the
app. We've been partnering with Figma
on it and it basically just like helps
the model use it a bit better. So
I can just take a link,
basically copy the link from what I'm
working on in Figma. So like we can
open it up here. So I'll go ahead and
I'll just take this link here
and I'll just paste
it in here and then I'll click up.
So this will work a little bit. We can
have a look at what it's doing while
it's going and this will, you know,
just kind of refresh in real time. And
this is the magic of using like a hot
reload. Yes, so you can kind of
monitor as Codex is going. Pretty
good. Let's have a look. Let's have a
look at the original design. So this
is the original design. Yeah, it's
used my entire design system as well.
So these are buttons from the design
system. You know, this was here before
and, you know, it's used the same
ones. And this is a good example of
where like, you know, it was like 90 %
of the way there. So I would just
maybe like remove a few of these
borders. You know, I would adjust some
of the styling. I would make it look a
little bit, you know, more like this
chat on the left. You know, I'd
probably like implement like a click
out here. But like these are really
like, you know, it's getting like 80 %
of the way there. And that's helping
remove like, I don't know, like two,
three times as fast. So it's just like
a very cool way to prototype extremely
quickly, particularly in a world of
LLMs where the output of LLMs is so
dynamic and non -deterministic. If
you're designing for AI, it's very
hard to do it in these static figures
and other things like this alone.
They're a great way to get it started.
But ultimately you want to stress test
it, which is why we've built
Interactive Prototype so that you can
see all these edge cases. And this is
just like an incredible prototype tool
to get started.